Hello Guys, Welcome to my YouTube channel.
My name is Arpit.  I hope you
all are well.  So today I am going to
tell you about a device which is
very important for the safety of our car nowadays.
By the way, you must have
recognized which device I am
talking about by looking at the thumbnail.  So yes, this is the
ISS.  So well, nowadays everyone is buying cars.
So nowadays when we
buy a car, the most
important thing after buying the car is its
insurance.  So,
over damage insurance is available for one year.  So
post that we have to get it renewed again.
So it was the same with me too.  I had a
car and my insurance had expired.  So I got it
renewed again.  Earlier
I had Reliance General.  So now I have
opted for ICICI,
nowadays everyone buys a car, so after buying the car,
insurance plays a major role,
after that when we buy insurance, then the
insurance also has to be renewed, the same thing happened
with me, I had Reliance
General insurance.  Now I am
moving to ICICI, so when I
took ICICI insurance, Zero Depth Insurance,
I got this device with it.
So this is ICICI's IL Assist powered by
Car IQ so manufactured by Car
IQ and marketed by ICICI
Assist.
So I got this device free with insurance.
So I did
not have to pay any extra cost for this.  So
nowadays no one gives it for free.   It is
included in the insurance.  But they
show it as if
you have given Zero ₹ for the device.  So today I am going to
tell you about it, what
is this device?  What are its features?  How
can we install it.  So right now I'm going to
unbox it.  Well, I had checked it.
So once we unbox it.
So this is its box.  So ICICI
LBD IL Assist powered by Car IQ.
So if we look at the side, this is
some of its devices and if we look at the back, the
steps to follow are mentioned in it.  So the
first step is to download ILS Tap, then you
can install this application in both Android, Google Play and Apple.  After that I have
given you this smart plug.
You have to plug the smart plug into the device.
After that you have to connect and then your
device will start.
So after this post, you have given us the
toll free number below.  If you
face any issue with any device or need any assistance,
you can connect with the ICICI team through this toll free number.
So there
is nothing else left.  So let's start
unboxing it.
So this is its device.  So device pay
well device.  I had already told you that
this device has been made by Car IQ company,
it has been marketed
by ICICI people, so this is the
reading device ID of the device, this device ID
is such that when you open the app,
you have to link it by entering the device ID in the app,
so keep it on the side,
keep it on the side and this is the manual of the device on
how to install it.
So let me see in this,
firstly you have to download ICICI's IL Assist app, both
in Google Play and
App Store, I will put the links of both,
if you want to download it, then
after that the second step is to
register the username, which you will download in it,
when you purchase the plan Smart Plan from ICICI LB, then the
username and password will
come to your email ID.  What to do
after the password arrives on your email ID
?  When you open the IL Assist
application, you will have to login into it with your
username and password.
You will already get both the passwords on your email ID.
So post that, after that you will have to
read all its terms and conditions.  You will have to check mark it.
After that you will have to continue.   As soon as you
continue, do as you please.  So it
is mentioned here that you will have to
reset the password.  After resetting the password,
you will have to create a new password yourself.
In the fourth step and fifth step, you have to
mention the device ID given to you on your device.  After that the device will find it for
you.  After that you have to
click on the link.
Your device will be connected as soon as you click on the link.
And after that what you have to do is
install the device in your car.  So
how to install it in the car?  So it is also
mentioned in this to locate your OBD port.  If
this device is installed under the plastic dash panel of your car.
What happens in Hyundai is that there is
a panel at the bottom right side of the steering wheel side of the car.
You have to open it.
This OBD device got plugged inside it.  Ford is used
in Ford vehicles.  It is located
just below the steering wheel.  Ok?
Mostly in Ford vehicles at the bottom.  It is mentioned in it and similarly
in Tata Indica it is mentioned below the driver seat,
below the
driver seat in Tata Indica Indigo
and similarly if it is in the glove box
in Renault cars and
in Mahindra Verito it is mentioned in the glove box.
So, since I have a Renault
car, I will obviously have to keep it
inside the glove box.  I will have to
mention it.  Gotta put it.
So after that,
when you plug this device of yours,
an LED light will be activated in your device.
LED light will glow in it.
I don't know where it will burn.  Okay, the
LED light will glow here.  If the LED light
blinks in your smart plug,
it means that your device is properly
plugged in.  So what happens after that is that
you can check it in your app application as to
what all you can check.
It records your data.
How will tracking tell you in the data record.
What can
you track in it?  It will tell in kilometers.  The engine
will tell.  Engine Status: Are you facing any issue with the engine?  It will
also tell you at what speed you are
driving, how long you have
driven today and how many kilometers you have
driven.  Ok?  And after this it will
tell you the condition of the battery.  What is the condition of this battery
and is there any error in the engine?  It will
show complete details of your vehicle.
Will show engine details.  So there are many more
such features in it.  So let me
connect it once.  After that let us see what other
features you get in it.
In this you will get alerts that
any of your drives is your device.  If someone is taking you away,
where is he taking you?
You can check it.  So you
also have alerts with Jio graphic.  So let me
tell you in the next video how to
install it and how to use it
in the app.  Thank you so much.  So thank you so much.
So let's unbox it once again.
Well, I had checked it.  So let
me give this one another go to
show you.  I will unbox it once to
show you.  So here's some of its
box.
So let me unbox it once again.
Unboxing what?  I had already
opened it.  I'll
show you again anyway.  So this is its
box IL assist powered by Car IQ.
So it has a branding on the side.  IL
Assist has been mentioned.
Its steps are given below.  How do you follow
him?  First you have to download the Download Assist app.
You can download it in both Android, Google and Apple.
Post that, you will
find this smart plug inside it and
you have to connect it to your car.  Have to link.
After that your car will be connected
to your app.  After that your car will
also be secured.  So a
number is also given at the back like toll free number etc.
If you need some help regarding this device
or anything else.
You can make a call through ICICI app.  ICI will
help you as a customer.
So hello guys, so I am here in my car.  So
I want to show you.  This is the
device.  So today I want to tell you
how I install it
in the car.  So first of all, this has to be removed.  Let
me take this out in a minute.
So it's like a device.  This device
is like this.  So it has ports.  So
I want to show.  So in my car the
OBD port of the device is
inside the glove box.  I will remove this.
So as soon as I remove this device
I get this OBD port.
So let me plug this in once.
So it's properly plugged.  So let me
check this for a minute.
Yes, it is properly plugged.
Where will the I don't know light be lit in this?  So I want to see.
Ok.  This light of yours is on.  Is the
LED light blinking?  So this
means that it is properly plugged in.
As soon as you plug your device into the OBD port,
you will
turn on your application and enter your username and
password in it. As soon as
you enter the username and password in the ILAs app, you will login. As soon as
you login,
you will see the main page of the device. The dashboard
does not show you the card details immediately in the dashboard. It will take some time and you will have to refresh it two-three
times. As soon as you
refresh it, you will see the main page.  I did
not get the exact location of the car but he
gave me the details of my car to check if there was
any issue with the engine.
What is the voltage of the battery?  How long has it been since I started
driving?  So everything else was fine.  And
no light came on in my engine.  See
now as you will see there is no light in my engine also.
Look at this, it is
not even showing any error.  And after that,
as soon as you click on the side,
it will appear on the side menu of the app where these
three lines are made.  In that you will get complete
details like live location of the application
etc. of your car, it
takes time to sync.  After that, you see,
I did not see any error in the car's meter also.
Everything else is good.
If you like this video, please
like, comment and subscribe
to my channel.  Thank you.